

# Jaewon Lee

ROBOTICS · MULTI-ROBOT · SLAM

12 Seongsan-ro 22-gil, Seodaemun-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea

 $\square \ (+82) \ 10-9114-2756 \quad | \quad \blacksquare \ leejaewon@yonsei.ac.kr \quad | \quad \bigstar \ lee-jaewon.github.io \quad | \quad \blacksquare \ Lee-JaeWon$ 

"Passion is the genesis of genius."

## **Summary**

This is Jaewon Lee, who wants to be a Robotics researcher and engineer. I am interested in Robotics, SLAM, Multi-Robot System. I think Robotics can help the development of the world a lot. I want to study a lot and approach the world.

## Research Interests

**SLAM** Multi-Robot, Descriptor

**Novel View Synthesis** 3D Scene Representation, Sensor-Fused Representation

## Education

#### Yonsei University @CILAB

Seoul, S.Korea

COMBINED M.S. & Ph.D. IN ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING (ADVISOR: PROF. EUNTAI KIM)

Mar. 2024 -

• Research on Robotics

#### **KwangWoon University**

Seoul, S.Kored

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024

- GPA: 4.13/4.50, Major GPA: 4.29/4.50
- Club: BARAM Robotics (Robotics Academic Group) [2022 Vice President], Mar.2020-Feb.2024

# Work Experience\_

## Yonsei University @CILAB

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor: PROF. Euntai Kim)

Jul. 2023 - Feb. 2024

- I Participated in ICCV 2023 SLAM Challenge
- I studied 3D Scene Representation

#### **ROBOMATION**

Seoul, S.Korea

R&D Intern

Jun. 2022 - Aug. 2022

- I developed an automation system for soccer games using multi-robot.
- I developed multi-robot coordination and pose system using Aruco Marker.

## KwangWoon University @Robotics A.I. LAB.

2022.10 Dean's list, for Academic Excellence

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor : PROF. Junghyun Oh)

Jan. 2022 - Jun. 2022

- I studied visual SLAM and visual odometry
- I studied Multi-Robot system and implemented Multi-Robot exploration

### Honors & Awards

#### **AWARDS**

2023.12	2023 Hanium ICT Mentoring Competition, Silver Award	Ministry of Science and ICT, IITP, FKii
2023.10	ICCV 2023 SLAM Challenge, Fourth place in LiDAR-Inertial Track - Taeyoung Kim, Jaewon Lee, Beomsoo Kim, Euntai Kim	ICCV 2023
2023.06	Undergraduate Paper Award, Paper - Autonomous multi robot parking system	ICROS 2023

#### HONORS

2022.10 Full Tuition Scholarship, for the first place in last semester

Kwangwoon Univ.

## **Publication**

#### **DOMESTIC CONFERENCE**

"Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System", 2023.06

Jaewon Lee, Hyosuk Joo, Chung-gil Ahn, Hyedo Kim, Junghyun Oh - [Paper]

## Skills\_

**Programming** C++/C, Python, MATLAB DevOps ROS/ROS2, Docker, Git

**Framework** PyTorch, Tensorflow, Keras, Unity

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### Technical Blog - lee-jaewon.github.io

WRITER

Jul. 2021 - Present

- I have been writing posts about the paper review, development, the study of Interests.
- · To study through writing and sharing.
- The blog is available at [here].

#### **Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System**

Kwangwoon Univ.

CAPSTONE DESIGN

Jan.2023 - Jun.2023

- · Implement a multi-robot system and implement various technologies necessary for mobile robots.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

#### 2022 Open Source Contribution Academy

MENTEE

I contributed to translating PyTorch Hub English documents into Korean at the PyTorch Korean User's Group.

#### **Multi Robot Collision Avoidance with Velocity Obstacle**

Jul. 2022 - Oct. 2022

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2022 - Nov.2022

- I implemented collision avoidance with Velocity Obstacle using multi-robot.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

## **Autonomous Driving Simulation with Reinforcement Learning**

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2021 - Nov.2021

- I implemented an Autonomous-driving system through DQN algorithm for the high-way situation.
- I implemented a simulator with Unity. And I managed the reward using Laser Sensor.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

#### **Frontier Based Multi-Robot Exploration**

PERSONAL PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- I implemented ROS-based multi-robot frontier exploration.
- I implemented a multi-robot SLAM system using open sources.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

## **House Interior Classifier and Automatic Recommendation**

DEEP-LEARNING PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- I implemented House Interior Classifier using Inception-Resnet-V2 in Keras.
- · I implemented a system that can automatically search on the actual shopping site with the classified result.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].